<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Minimal</title><link>http://example.com/</link><description>Recent content on Minimal</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="http://example.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>CS 105 Programming Languages</title><link>http://example.com/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.com/</guid><description>Monday &amp;amp; Wednesday 04:00PM - 05:50PM Winter Hall, Room 110 Carroll Hall tent
Description Language processors; data; binding time; operations; sequence control; referencing environments; scope of a variable; storage management; operating environment, syntax; translation. From the 21-22 Westmont College Academic Catalog.
Textbook Concepts of Programming Languages, by Sebesta, R. E., 12th Edition, Pearson, 2019
Prerequisites CS 010 Design and Implementation of Solutions to Computational Problems CS 030 (Abstract Models for Concrete Problems Using Java) Grading In-Class Exercises 25% Homework / Projects 20% Group Project / Presentation 20% Midterm 15% Final 20% FALL 2021 Aug 30, Sep 1 Intro, Chapters 1-2 Sep 6, 8 Chapter 15: Functional Programming Sep 13, 15 Chapter 3: Describing Syntax and Semantics Sep 20 Chapter 4: Lexical and Syntax Analysis Sep 22 Guest Lecture: Robert McLaughlin (Regulator: Dynamic Analysis to Detect ReDos) Sep 27, 29 Chapter 5: Names, Bindings and Scopes Oct 4, 6 Chapter 6: Data Types Oct 11-12 FALL HOLIDAY Oct 13 Chapter 7: Expression and Assignment Statements Oct 18 Chapter 8: Control Structures Oct 20 Chapter 9: Subprograms Oct 25-27 Mid-Term, Chapter 9: Subprograms (part 2) Nov 1, 3 Chapter 10: Implementing Subprograms Nov 8 Chapter 12: Data Abstraction Nov 10, 15 Chapter 13: Concurrency Nov 17 Chapter 14: Exception &amp;amp; Event Handling Nov 22 Guest Lecture: Stijn Pletinckx (Out of Sight, Out of Mind: A Comprehensive Study on the Prevalence and Security Impact of Orphaned Web Pages) Nov 24-26 THANKSGIVING HOLIDAY Nov 29 Refactor code, review project release notes Dec 1, 6 Presentations Dec 8 STUDY DAY Dec 13 STUDY DAY Dec 15 Final EXAM 3-5pm Class Policies and Support Class participation: Attendance is recommended not only for learning the material, but for completing and turning in the in-class exercises.</description></item></channel></rss>